yo what's up everyone welcome to this
latest episode of critical thinking bug
bunny podcast as always I'm your host
Justin Gardner and co-host Joel Margolis
is currently not here today so we
brought on a great guest Corbin Leo
amazing hacker wonderful methodology so
I think you'll really enjoy what he's
got to say this episode
um but before we dive into it I wanted
to ask you to head over to
criticalthinkingpodcast.io And subscribe
to our newsletter what that's going to
do is it's going to give you access to a
text version of the content that we've
been producing here produced by none
other than Jesse Rivera himself so
during the nice little intro song that
we've got here pull out your phone head
over to
criticalthinkingpodcast.io and drop
subscribe hope you enjoy the episode
[Music]
okay
yo yo yo welcome to the Pod Corbin
thanks thanks for having me excited to
be here thanks for stepping in last
minute we had uh no worries we had Joel
disappear on us this week he had some
family stuff coming up so I texted
Corbin yesterday at like 9pm be like yo
can you get on the Pod tomorrow morning
so appreciate you stepping in Man of
course
all right
um so I've got a bunch of questions for
you and uh I hope did you did you grab a
report by the way
yeah I have one in mind okay cool nice I
was gonna I was gonna go to my my uh
collaboration stuff and see if we could
find one uh that we worked on together
but um yeah if you've got one that works
too
um okay so first let's go ahead and do
the new section so how this works Corbin
is we we first we do the news and then I
ask you a bunch of questions that I've
got in the doc about your life and your
hacker hacker Vibes but since we've got
no Jill today you're stepping in and
you're doing the news with us
um alrighty so first thing that I had a
list here and this is pretty cool
um I really I really like just DNS
rebinding as a as a concept
um but there was an article that came
out earlier this week called state of
DNS rebinding in 2023
um and actually I think he got released
uh actually about a month ago now but it
just came across my feed this was by uh
an NCC group
and
um essentially it's it's exactly what it
sounds like a state of DNS rebinding um
article and it talks about all the
different
um sort of restrictions that they have
in the space
um there's local network requests which
is a uh sort of a new restriction
um that's coming in into place
unfortunately like in this upcoming
version of Chrome we're about to lose
access to a bunch of local network stuff
um
yeah uh but it's it's uh just to sort of
summarize it it's going to start there's
going to be some core stuff that's going
to start coming in into play on local
local
um network access and uh this is already
in what is called a
um
Chrome depreciation trial
um which essentially allows for us to
have a developer token that you request
if you still need this feature so that
they can still like sort of gradually
roll it out and not break everything so
that was something I'd never heard of
before and I thought was pretty
interesting
um let's see what else is there here
um yeah I think all these bug Bounty
programs are in outdated versions of
chrome still right yeah I know right
yeah
they still they still have like uh you
know a lot of times that what you run
into in those sort of situations is like
super mega old Crohn's and that becomes
the problem right it's like oh man how
do I hack this thing that doesn't have
any of the features I've been used to
for the past you know six or seven
versions
um let me see what else I had here on
the notes so yeah this is something that
we talked about when we did the episode
um on uh rebind multi-a
um and uh that is that Chrome can there
is a rebind that you can do do in Chrome
that's instant with using a a record
um that has multiple IP addresses that
it resolves to
um and that can rebind only to local or
only to 0.0.0.0 which is like sort of a
private IP address I mean technically
you can access local services but it's
not necessarily I'm specifically a
loopback or a local IPA address space so
there's a um there's a chrome issue that
will link in the description
um saying specifically you know tracking
that specific vulnerability but as of
right now the takeaways from that
article are that you can still attack
surfaces on 0.0.0.0 using Singularity or
my DNA history binding tool and then the
other thing that I I didn't know
was that the websocket port scanner
still works so you can still do timing
attacks against local
services and and services on the local
network using a websocket port scanner
which I thought was pretty rad
um let's see what else we got here
um
yeah so let's see douglas douglas day uh
arc Arc Angel D-Day is his Twitter
handle posted a a Twitter thread which I
know Corbin loves right
haha it's been a while yeah yeah
um and he dropped 100 very short bug
Bounty rules and I think at the end of
the Tweet he kind of linked to
uh Ryan holiday tweet
um where he got that sort of uh
flow from but this is a really cool
um tweet that has a bunch of really nice
advice for uh what you would do if if
you were you know 100 different rules
for bug Bounty and what kind of stuff
you should try to approach
um so I figured let's go ahead and and
take a peek at these real quick uh
Corbin and and read through some of
these and give these a talk so
um one of the ones that popped out to me
was uh give yourself a no bug limit I do
three hours so he said that like if you
don't find a bug within three hours on a
specific part of the topic or Target you
you move along what do you think about
that man
I mean I think that's I think that makes
sense I mean I don't think I'd I don't
do three hours maybe I should but it's
just like okay I'm kind of sick of
looking at this I'm gonna look at
something else so you move along pretty
quickly
yeah I move on decently decently quickly
okay gotcha let's see what's like a
really big app if it's bigger then it's
like okay I don't see anything I don't
know I tend to
like some people do more of like
pantester methodology where it's like
okay I'm gonna test this specific thing
for literally everything whereas it's
like okay I'm gonna like just check out
the different functionality and then I'm
gonna like I don't know go where like my
Spidey senses like are tingling in one
area so like I'm gonna go look at this
and then okay I don't see anything here
and I just kind of do that I feel like
you have a pretty strong hacker spidey
sense which I think you know we'll we'll
touch on a little bit later in the flow
but I'm definitely interested in trying
to trying to crack that nut a little bit
because when I read through your threads
and just when I've seen you you know at
the live hacking events and such I feel
like you find bugs that are pretty
different from what I find so I think
our our methodology sort of deviates a
little bit there and you're a little bit
a little bit more Recon heavy which is
cool
um let's see what else we got here oh
okay so this is another one that I
thought was pretty cool uh 24 uh it says
six six 1K mediums pay more than one 5K
crit don't ignore any bugs and I think
this one is kind of like once because
there's a certain brand of hacker that
just kind of only reports highs in crits
and that's great but I totally agree
with with Douglas here that there are a
lot of people and even ignoring lows I
think is is a mistake because one that's
value you could have in your pocket and
two
what the company is going to pay for it
it's something that they want it's
something that they think would secure
up their attack surface so I would say
never never don't report a bug that you
think might be valid
yeah and I I agree with that I mean
there's sometimes
I guess it kind of depends
um
like if you find a stumble across medium
or low bug
why would you not report it because it's
just like yeah you might get duped but
hey if like there's a chance you're not
and I guess that's like free money
but yeah then there's other people that
just don't even look for mediums or
anything like lower than that too yeah
but I don't know I Stumble Acron across
mediums or lows when I'm looking for
higher impact yeah same here that's
that's the kind of thing that I I like
you know when I'm and I've talked about
this on our on our episode um I'll have
to pull it up right here
um the episode where we talk about how
to find a good program episode 13.
um I kind of talk about this you know
whenever I'm choosing a program I always
try to pick a program that has good
payments for lows and mediums as well
because as you're going after those
highs and crits you're always going to
stumble upon the lows and the mediums
and it's just nice to to have a good
consistent you know influx of bounties
coming in to keep you motivated and to
keep your you know wallet full if you're
a full-time bike bounty hunter yep
exactly I think like the the inverse of
this problem too is like when you're
only looking for like lows and mediums I
don't know people who like I I guess I
don't know if like anyone specifically
who does that but
um I mean I guess that's a mistake too
is I guess that might just be like
trying to like crack to find like bigger
and bigger things
um so yeah yeah I don't know I think I
think it I think it can I think it can
go you know if if you're just not
dreaming big enough in your attack
Vector mentality as well like if you're
never thinking like for example I I very
rarely I used to very rarely look for
um uh arbitrary account takeover right
because I was like this bug is just kind
of like a myth right like does this
really exist though and then like you
know I see you and uh oh X ACV and some
of the other hackers out there that just
kind of have a a different mentality
start popping some of this stuff at life
hacking events and I'm like oh wow
literally oxacv I like I I love it man
he literally I think you know the one
I'm talking about yeah I know exactly
what you're talking about that one is
actually insane that was yeah and it was
just I thought that could be done like
literally 15-year Legacy code where he
popped an arbitrary kind take over just
because it was like a it was like a
string contains bug rather than a string
equals bug which is crazy
um so that one was yeah that one blew my
mind I think keeping keeping the attack
Vector mentality high is another really
good solid tip well yeah and also don't
like put restrictions on ideas before
you try it too it's like oh there's no
way that could work it's like you'd be
surprised by how much code is just like
strung together
yeah with who knows what devs devs do
crazy [__] sometimes yeah they really do
exactly and there's just weird services
that interpret things differently like
you never know yeah so I knew I I know I
kind of threw this on you last second
here with the Tweet but you see any of
these that that stand out to you in
particular
um let me see
I mean I think
let's see
uh um
let's see 36. you find a bug that's out
of scope
like this is a whole another this 36 you
could talk about so much more too is
like
what is it if you find a bug that's out
of scope still ask the customer if they
care
um I've I don't know that's a really
tough tough one because like there's
obviously reasons you have scope
sections in you know Perkins horoscope
sections you don't want them hacking you
know like third party
um obviously there's like you might find
an RC on something but like it it's
contained as a Sandbox it has like
access to nothing there's plenty of
still like out of scope things that have
like an insane impact that the customer
might not know about too
um yeah
so you say don't ask the customer if
they care just submit the bug or what do
you what are you saying not necessarily
it's like
I don't know it's really difficult
because
um
like you shouldn't just go like hacking
out of scope stuff just for the sake of
hacking out of scope stuff
um
but at the same time I don't know I
don't want to get into this yeah
I mean
there's lots of times I've had some
pretty good bugs by going a bit out of
scope and and to be fair it's a program
that has like that has had a VIP section
where they have only a certain number of
assets return scope for the VIP pain
program they also have a VDP it's like
without that program
um it's a lot easier to do this
um but I've had like instances of like a
domain that isn't even related to that
company
um and it was actually it turns out it
was owned by them
um but it was somehow linked to this
like one asset this like production
database of all their like customers and
it was like
um
this huge like information leakage and
that was by some like it was way out of
scope I don't even think it was listed
in their like VDP program but it was
still owned by them
um and so like that one was paid for
their Max
uh like a Max crit inside their VIP
program even that wasn't even like list
and scope wow but then I've also had
like
another companies all have like internal
host names that they use for networking
you know inside like kubernetes pods
just within their like corporate Network
um and there'll be times that there's
like assets that are still on the
internet with like SSL certificates
linked to those and you can still hit
those and like there's like
vulnerabilities on those apps that like
okay it's not listed in scope but hey
this is like really bad this is like
internal like infrastructure there's
like lots of like sensitive information
oh you can find like bugs in these apps
where it's like really bad and they
still care about that I feel like that's
kind of crazy what's that you know right
because like if they list something and
you never really know for sure unless
you know unless you're internal but if
they list something like okay www is in
scope in www is just reverse proxy to
this back end you know
um API that they have that is on a
different domain and so literally
everything that WWE every piece of
functionality that www has
um you know is getting routed through
this this API but that back end piece if
you access it directly it's not in scope
that doesn't really make any sense yeah
it's like yeah like example.com API is
actually just reverse proxy to
api.example.com scope and it's just like
I don't know it gets
it gets weird it does get weird it does
get weird fast there I think um and I
think one other one that just popped out
to me and then we'll move along to the
next next little thing here is
um
if an app is number 28 if an app uses
uuids you can still look for idors just
set AC to high and I think this is one
of one of the the mistakes that I made
early on is not realizing that it is
that you know some programs will say Hey
you uuid idors aren't going to be a
thing but that's literally what the
attack complexity High metric was made
for is like hey there's some piece of
this attack that requires some some
state to be some the application to be
in some state or some piece of
information that I don't know but it's
reasonable for me to get and so um you
know these these sort of IDs in these
idore scenarios aren't really being
treated as sensitive information and so
um it's definitely I think Falls within
the scope of AC access control high
to be fair I wouldn't really even call
it I don't know if I'd call it an idol
or if I just call it like an access
control bug oh really
I don't know
yeah maybe not I mean I guess it is
still I guess an eye door I just think
like when people think of idors because
that means like you're still yeah and
you're just
referencing another object but I mean
like
I don't know I guess with a lot of
programs
um
like a lot of people just when they
think of idors think it's like okay I
can just like increment document a
number
um and sometimes like I've had success
where I just say like hey it's an access
control bug and it kind of clicks for
them because they're like oh wait you
can't just easily get this like euid but
like you can find ways to click it still
um so and you're like still shouldn't be
able to access it so sometimes just like
framing it like access control issue or
like lack of like access control like
something like that it's just like an
easier way to present it to someone who
might you know
just not yeah yeah not get the full the
full picture for sure yeah and that kind
of goes into like 41 when you just as
like spend the extra time making your
report look or read nice just write well
right clearly yeah
um because I mean this whole thing's
about communication so funny you should
mention that Corbin because I have on my
list of notes about you know about you
when I did my little you know OS in on
Corvin before this episode I I one of
the things that really stood out to me a
lot is your your propensity for
storytelling and writing
um and combining that with hacking
um and so
um tell you what let's finish the new
section and then I'll come I'll come
back to that real quick okay no worries
real quick so definitely check out that
that tweet by um
arching art it's arc angle Arch
please say it for me Corbin please like
Archangel Archangel thank you I couldn't
say art and angles
geez sorry sorry you know like I get
that um Arch Arc Archangel D-Day is his
handle on Twitter go check it out it's a
great great tweet okay um next one that
I wanted to talk about was um this
service called TalkBack
um this is actually put out by ltam uh
one of the the companies that we
mentioned uh before on the Pod and this
is just a news aggregator for um cyber
security related infosec related content
and I've just got this favorited and
I'll pop this open every couple days and
just kind of scroll through the last
couple days of of news um I just wanted
to throw that out there because it seems
like a pretty good resource um it's not
necessarily before yeah it's pretty I
don't think it's caught on as much so
I'm hoping that people will start using
it a little bit more and dumb and yeah
it's not necessarily bug Bounty oriented
um but it is you know infosec oriented
so for those of you that have a little
bit broader Horizon than just bug Bounty
um that's a good place to look
um let's see uh last thing on the news
item for today was
um pie pie
uh just released recently that they are
going to uh enforce mandatory 2fa for
all software Publishers and I think this
is a great idea
um I think that this is something that
should have been implemented a while
back and I think this will really help
with the whole
um it's not necessarily dependency yeah
exactly supply chain attacks not
necessarily dependency confusion but
it's like a scenario where you can take
over the account of a person that has
um I'm done you know is the author of a
certain Pi Pi Library
um so I think 2fa on this is really
Gonna Make a Difference yeah that'll be
huge from just like even
attacks where you know like someone's
social engineer is a domain registrar
yeah
um that happens
yes this is all sorts of other things
besides that too but that's a really
good idea yeah surprised that wasn't
yeah it would be huge yeah I'm surprised
it wasn't implemented before either that
that definitely seems like a no-brainer
thing but I I do wonder what's going to
happen if they don't have that you know
like for example if if somebody just
doesn't update their 2fa and they just
never log into their pie account are
they gonna prevent them from like
pushing updates to it or you know
something like that could be could be
interesting to see yeah it would be very
interesting I wonder if there's npm do
this I don't I don't I don't know I feel
like they should
I feel like it definitely should yeah I
think it's not mandatory
um but it is something that you can
configure see and I'm glad pipei has
sort of taken the first step and moving
in that direction kind of setting the
industry standard you know my beloved
language python just happens to be just
doing everything right so I love to see
that
um dude I love it man I really do I
still I still write python every day
it's it's the best
um okay so news section done Corbin
switches from co-host to guest
um so
man we've been hacking together for
probably five years at this point
um and I don't know that I've ever heard
the whole like how did you get into bug
Bounty story uh you know I know we've
run into each other at live hacking
events but like you know my back story
is Tommy Tommy DeVos just rolled into my
you know cyber security class and just
started teaching about bug Bounty
randomly
um without even being invited to the
best of my knowledge uh oh that's so
funny I know he just showed up one day
and I was like uh hello
um but yeah what's what's yours how did
you hear about bug Bounty and and uh
that whole industry
well I didn't know I'd gotten into like
hacking when I was a freshman in high
school
um
but I didn't know bug Bonnie was a thing
or that you could even do ethical legal
hacking until I was a junior in high
school okay
um and I had I was on Twitter and I saw
someone's tweet I think it might have
been Tommy too I think oh really yeah I
ordered ten thousand dollars why is he
such everyone's origin story
yeah and so he was like he someone I
think he tweeted out like a big Bounty
amount that he got from like Yahoo or
something sure I was like what like
that's a lot of money or he did this for
what yeah and so then like I clicked on
the link that was in the in the tweet
and then I like came across hacker one
I'm like whoa you can get paid to report
vulnerabilities so I signed up for
hacker one and gave it a test
um
it was a struggle at first I thought it
was like a god at hacking yeah yeah
that's something that'll humble you
really quickly yeah
and so yeah then I started doing bug
bounties kept after it and yeah here I
am okay so so you literally I mean you
didn't really know any other in-person
bug bounty hunters you just kind of
found it on Twitter and then kind of
rolled into it yep I had no idea about
what what it was so like I I think I
followed taught me on Twitter
um
I found some other like bug bounty
hunters on Twitter and just like started
following them yeah
um yeah I just signed a Tracker one I
read through some like I looked I I like
there's no hacker 101 at that point
either you know no there wasn't no there
wasn't that there wasn't any like pen
tester I don't think there was like
pentester lab or like any of those like
courses and stuff so like I had taught
myself
to hack before that
um
a lot of going through like exploit DB
stuff oh yeah Classics yeah and then
um a lot of just like reading tutorials
and like reading people's like Twitter
posts blogs
um then just like trying to trial and
error so nice I spent a lot of time on
like the dod program yeah first started
I mean I started on like public programs
to try to do like bug bounties and then
like I just failed miserably
um so I tried like Department of Defense
and I got like tons of dupes from that
but it was like really good experience
in practicing it's so funny man I I
think I'm getting notifications right
now from like four years ago
that of them closing bugs that I
reported four years ago and I'm like on
one hand like that's kind of impressive
that you're actually still tracking this
bug yeah but on the other hand like wow
four years like
um so I mean do you endorse the the
DOD VDP to bug Bounty you know sort of
like a training ground for actual bug
Bounty for like you receive a bounty bug
Bounty
um methodology or would you do it
differently if you went back
would I do it differently than what I
did like originally yeah I mean so if
you were advising someone to start now
would you say go ahead and start on the
the dod program or would you say you
know try to just go and go straight
after bug bounty
hard one I would say
I don't think you can go wrong with
either
I mean it took me 10 months to get my
first Bounty but that was okay for me
because I was a high schooler I was just
doing it my free time like right during
school it's kind of just hacking for fun
um so I mean like if you have prior
experience
yeah like for me I didn't have tons of
like I didn't have as in high school it
didn't have that much experience with
computers
um sure packing didn't have like so I
feel like you already work as like
security engineer there's some pretty
solid fundamentals I mean why would you
not just go for
um
go for just any like normal blood Money
program I think for people who are
wanting to work on like fundamentals
um just
All That Jazz I would say like work on
recon all that
just get a very good like solid
understanding of different vulnerability
classes different Technologies and stuff
I'd say go for the Department of Defense
because they have all sorts of stuff
yeah um they do have a lot of different
stacks and I think also you can see your
origin uh you know a little bit clearly
in your current attack Vector
methodology because you know like you
almost have sort of like a like a Jason
Haddix ish flow of like all right I'm
gonna do x amount of Recon and I'm gonna
find like these weird you know aspf
endpoints that are like no one ever
thought was real yeah you know and and
and it's not necessarily like
um
and you know don't get me wrong I've
seen you YouPorn new companies and old
companies alike but um you know I feel
like the dod having such a wide scope
having such an array of Technologies and
being a little bit more outdated sort of
LED you down the path to being you know
focusing really hard on recon and having
that be a key part of your methodology
would you agree with that yeah yeah I'd
say that and then hacking a lot with
like naffi that'll be entered me a ton
so like yeah I have a lot of like naffy
like mentality when it comes to like
infrastructure and stuff like that too
um so yes any any tidbits on that you
want to share I think nappy is an
interesting character and we'll probably
have him on the Pod at some point but
his hacking methodology is definitely
um pretty pretty different from a lot of
what I've seen yeah no he
he finds apps that no one would have
ever found and just completely destroys
them once he's found them that's what I
love about it it's like okay just like
you make yours you make new
opportunities for yourself and then
so I mean what does that entail
I mean I don't want to give his away
okay well it's yours now too I remember
hold on I remember this deal though uh
that you had with naffy a while back and
and if we have to cut this section we
can but you know there was a deal that
y'all made about naffy working with you
and him getting a certain percent of
your Bounty and yeah you guys were
working at a life hacking event together
yeah and that was like what that was I
think it was that maybe it was that one
that was probably like four or five
years ago right
2019-ish yeah four years ago so yeah I
feel like the I feel like the statue of
limitations on that is up I mean I mean
if you don't want to Dos your secrets
that's I mean or doctor secrets that's
fine you know if you don't want to
disclose all that but
um yeah I I just I think it's really
interesting I know that uh naffy's
approach is largely a virtual host
enumeration based in a lot of scenarios
which is something that not a lot of
people poke at and um I think mapping
out the in internal routing
um on a company can result in some crazy
stuff so oh yeah absolutely is that
still a part of your methodology
yeah I look a lot at load balancers I
play a lot with load balancers and just
like different Ingress endpoints and I
mean the nice thing is like when you do
it for a long time you can kind of start
noticing like
how
apps work and then also just like if
you've been in like software development
or I guess um
architecture I guess like if you're
finding it yeah if you've ever played
like kubernetes
um set up like infrastructure on that
it's like you you get a pretty solid
understanding of just how you know how
it's made how everything works and I
mean start poking at stuff so welcome to
this episode of How It's Made with
Corbin How It's Made
um and so okay so how are you how are
you identifying a load balancer is that
are you just doing virtual hosts scans
and seeing if multiple stuff pop up and
then
it kind of depends on the technology
right
um so like with Amazon you'll have like
cdnance to like elb oh nice I mean you
can look at like
you can look at headers
um like response headers will make it
obvious there's what kind of stuff have
you seen in response so just to click on
what he just said just a second ago if
there's a c name to a uh on a host to a
um Amazon uh endpoint that has elb in
the in the domain name uh as a result of
the cname then that's elastic load
balancer and that's going to be clearly
doing some load balancing right and then
you said in the response headers there's
some stuff that might be might be there
yep so like you'll see maybe like
um let's see like
for instance like with Kong you'll see
like a header that has that Kong in it
and that's like an Ingress you'll see
like okay so it'll it'll disclose the
technology stuff so like it can it can
do that um then there's other times
where like headers aren't and then
you'll just know like
default
responses like back end not found or
something like that um okay
and then it's just like trying it on a
few apps and seeing like if there's like
header like if
um
you can also just like
I'm kind of thinking how like fafaf does
or F off I'll probably say I hate I hate
I can't pronounce it
yeah if you like set
um you can do like like how FF does like
Auto calibration see like send a couple
HTTP requests different house headers
see how it responds and if it varies
like maybe you'll try it um fuzzy in
there but hmm
nice yeah it's It's Tricky man I I
definitely don't don't
I I started doing that a little bit uh
on some apps on some specific targets
that I know are vulnerable to it and uh
it's it's not and I even tried to build
some automation around it at some point
starting and this is something that I'll
tell people that are building out the
Recon flows nowadays is like you know if
you have a bunch of hosts that Matt you
know those hosts are not necessarily
only going to map to the IP addresses
that they resolve to so in your in your
sort of Recon framework in your recon
architecture you should be
um building in this functionality that
is going to be allowing you to map
domains to IP addresses right
um and I think that that makes a big it
makes a big difference because you can
find you know different domains are
accessible on different IP addresses
than the things they resolve to which
could give you different access
you agree
yeah and I mean like a lot of it yeah a
lot of it isn't even like V hosting too
it's just like okay this
um
this host name might point to
like Akamai or something like IP that
doesn't resolved but like the chances
are is that that IP might still be
exposed and it's just like
the way they're routing it is defined
this way but this host is still hearing
you use access it this way so sure nice
um solid okay well that that's that's
some good tips if you're if you're
trying to to keep an eye out for the
sort of the host realm and enumerate
some internal internal assets um using
that
um so you know you started off in book
Bounty uh you know you just signed up
for the website it took 10 months to get
your first Bounty and then you started
rolling how did you win in the live
hacking event circuit
um that's a good question I think it was
I
after I started getting more comfortable
with bug bounties I started looking at
Yahoo
um and so I started hacking on Yahoo a
bit and had like some xxes I got like an
xxc a couple ssrfs
um and then I think
my first event
might have been
there was one in New York yeah and it
was a team event it's like the only team
event that was your first event yeah I
think it was my first event I'm fairly
sure
I guess we had worked together before
then at that point then because I I feel
like I knew you at that at that point
yeah because I think like I knew I knew
you a new Sam yeah
I think that yeah I'm pretty sure that I
can't remember what other event would
have been oh no my first live hacking
event
I was not a hacker that's when I was
triaging a hacker one that's right okay
okay okay now it's starting to look at
the picture yeah it's making yeah making
more sense to me so I've been hacking on
Yahoo for a bit
and then I had done a semester of
college then I dropped out of college
and was traging at hacker one for like
six or seven
[Music]
hmm six seven maybe maybe eight months I
think it was less than that
um but I was traging at one of the first
uh or my first live event I was the one
of the Vegas events at 702 so I was
doing triage there that track I'd
already known people from like hacking
with them as well so yeah that that
definitely attracts so yeah that's an
interesting path like I feel I feel
I I've sort of recommended this to some
of my friends that are trying to get
into bug Bounty and are are also not
necessarily in love with the fact that
bug Bounty doesn't have consistent
income is that hey if you get started
you get rolling you start understanding
how Vols can be reproduced and you start
understanding
um you know it'll add a little bit more
technical level and you jump into a
triage role that can really boost your
game
um yeah I would agree you you would
agree with that I definitely also helps
you like learn even how to write better
reports down the line
um yeah definitely definitely I would
also recommend that to people who are
yeah that boat as an as an extrager here
what what is uh what is some of the
stuff that we do that's hella annoying
from the from the triager side from the
triage side it would be like there's
people who just write like you just give
you like the URL or they just like write
the most
basic Report with like no information I
think it's gotten a bit different
I don't know how like
because this is like four four or five
years this was a long this was five
this was in 2018. yeah yeah so five
years ago now math yeah yeah
um so I think yeah one of the biggest
irks I guess was just like the lack of
writing that some people did they like
just give you this
um
at that point in time at that point in
time did you have to rewrite the report
for the customer yeah okay so we had our
own like internal templates and internal
expectations of like what we had to
write and provide so like people would
also write like 10 pages
yeah and then we had to condense that to
like we got to pick every like the
important parts out and give like a very
clear concise like reproduction here's
the impact
stuff like that dude hacker one needs to
start training hacker world needs to
start training like their own offline
you know model llm model to to be able
to do that because that would be pretty
nice to just be like okay
um you know here's this like you know
Alex Chapman 25 page report and and I
need to condense this down to like you
know a page or two customer that'd be
that would be pretty good yeah or like a
hacker one grammarly yeah right that
would be really good I'm sure you can't
use actual grammarly at an ad hacker one
yeah that's probably not yeah that makes
sense that's one thing I said is that
could be really cool to have like a
language model
um
like fine-tune to my specific writing
style I'd be be amazing yeah but you can
train it a little bit I've done some of
the stuff um for the pod
just sort of taking the writing that
we've done
um you know with descriptions and titles
and stuff like that and then it just
takes the actual content of the podcast
and then you know it says all right you
know here are six suggestions for the
title or you know here are three
different rewrites of the description
and stuff like that and I think that
just provides a nice little
um you know jump off point and I and I
trained it with um the previous you know
titles and descriptions and stuff like
that too so it still has the same sort
of voice and that sort of thing and I
think I think llms do a pretty good job
of keeping the voice consistent across
um you know multiple bodies of text so
that's pretty rad
um solid okay
um so I guess as you left triaging eight
months you know Max after you after you
started why why did you do that and uh
how do you feel about the triage or
realm nowadays
um no I
it was a good experience but I was
getting kind of burnt out of it and my
parents wanted me to go back to school
when we go to college
um I didn't really want to go to college
but
um I was like screw it it's kind of fun
just to I guess be a kid and not have
responsibilities yeah for sure and so um
yeah I decided to transfer to a school
out in South Dakota and
yeah I mean it was it was a good
experience
um but I'm really glad I went back to
school not necessarily just because like
I needed education yeah it was just like
a fun experience in general where I just
got to meet nice so so you you went you
grew up in
was it Minnesota yeah Minnesota
Minnesota and then you went out of state
I went out of state to South Dakota so
South Dakota for those of you that are
not in the U.S though South Dakota is
like
there there's like there's nothing in
South there is there's Mount Rushmore I
think is in part of South Dakota yeah
it's on the west rapid but like like
South Dakota is like one of the least
popular and populated states in in the
US so what made you move from Minnesota
and instead of going out of state to any
other state what what made you land on
South Dakota
yeah so it was not trying to diss your
your new state here I'm just saying no I
know I know got to provide the content
it's pretty unique it's super yeah super
super unique and like whenever I tell
someone I'm from South Dakota yeah just
like super confused yeah like wait and I
think like North Dakota or there's two
Dakotas yeah exactly but um yeah so it
was July when I decided I wanted to be
done with
um
triaging I believe and I had thought
about going to either school in
Minnesota
um but it was so late that a lot of
schools didn't have transfers up anymore
and so there there was one school I'd
heard of
um
in South Dakota that was known for cyber
security for some reason oh cool um and
that's not what I was gonna go for like
I went for computer science but I was
like hey these people like at least will
like hacking like I like hacking or at
least I'll find some people that are at
least interested in the same time sure
sure I'm in the head applications open
super late so I just like applied to
transfer and they yeah they accepted
nice yeah and then so then I just yeah
went out there on a whim just kind of my
second like why not I guess yeah so
that's left to home but also new and how
did you enjoy that like I I feel like
that's one of the things that I
I don't really
endorse nowadays is like going to
college for the sake of going to college
but I think lately my my opinions have
been kind of coming back around of like
you know while you're young you don't
have to grind grind grind you know uh
and yeah you know go hard on the career
stuff you can actually just go and enjoy
and college is you know a great place to
meet other friends participate in club
activities that sort of thing yeah so if
you're still looking to grow as a person
College might be a good place to do it
yeah no I would agree with that I mean
it's hard too because it's I guess it
can be expensive yeah right yeah for
sure I mean I
I definitely enjoyed it I don't think
I like to like the computer science
stuff I didn't really
I don't think I'd ever needed like the
education I think it was is good
um
I wouldn't rely on it just to get to
where you want to be um like I would
never just go through courses and expect
you know to to pop out no exactly yeah
yeah to like come on like oh yeah and
everything I'm ready for this is like I
think if you really want to learn or get
it get anything that you have to spend
the time doing it yourself personally
totally um especially in the tech space
is like things move so quickly and
Technologies change
um
so yeah I mean I think if you want to
grow as a person
um meet some really great friends and
just like really I guess and enjoy your
life like I definitely would recommend
College still because
I mean you have your entire life to to
grind you might as well you know enjoy
some time
um yeah going from that like you know
younger younger like high schooler age
where you think you're an adult but then
you like finish college you're like wow
I'm a totally different person than I
was back then yeah I think's good for
like I guess character development first
yeah for sure it definitely is and and
yeah I think that is something that that
I you know from an early age was also
very career oriented and so I think I
think that having that extra you know
time to to grow and figure out who you
are not a bad not a bad not a bad route
just to say the least well yeah it gives
you a lot of times to like um
I guess experiment with what you really
want to do too right so that's true um
like for instance for me like it gave me
so much time to do bug bounties and also
like
just like develop my skills and that
like you can learn I guess whatever you
want you have plenty of like free time
to
you know explore Hobbies or experience
with your life yeah yeah for sure so I
know I know you did you just said you
did compsi as well yeah yep yeah so I I
did compsai as well I have to say you
know from a hacker perspective
I feel like a lot of the stuff that I
learned in Cobb site is an incredibly
relevant like if I want to go and do
software engineering and I want to like
really optimize this algorithm and get
like the you know there you go
complexity down you know whatever then
it'd be really great to have Computer
Science Background but a lot of a lot of
um hacking isn't really about that and
it's more about understanding the full
flow of everything right and I think I
think that's why compsize better than a
cyber security degree right it's like I
don't think you don't really need
like that's that's why I'd always
recommend like comp PSI if someone
doesn't know exactly what like they want
to do because it's just like it it lays
down a very solid like Baseline
um but
again it's like I don't think he even
needed a degree yeah yeah it's just more
so it's like I like if we're going to
like talk about degrees and like getting
one I'd say computer science just
because of like the fundamentals rather
than like oh we're just gonna learn how
to hack it's like wait you still need
all these like yeah fundamentals to get
good at it right yeah I totally agree
with that I think I think unless you're
going to a really like reputable cyber
security institution you know then I
think it may be better for you to focus
specifically on compsi and then
supplement with your own
um you know certificate-based training
towards cyber security but actually
Corbin I'm gonna I'm gonna disagree with
you on the on this one because I think
personally this is the this is the
hierarchy right here you've got you've
got uh cyber security degree you've got
computer science degree and you've got
Computer Engineering degree and I think
it's like yeah okay okay so I think all
of the people that I like for example
Joel and um Sam herb and like some of
the other really like just yeah I feel
like I I talk to these guys and they're
like yeah man I remember like you know
when I was desoldering this thing from
this board in in college I'm like what
like you know yeah my school didn't have
Computer Engineering yeah that would
have been a fun that would have been
yeah and I feel like even even the
people that I met at my school that were
doing computer engineering instead of
computer science I was like man these
guys just have a little bit of a deeper
understanding of like just like lower
lower level Concepts you know even lower
yeah and and I think having better
Baseline yeah exactly and even better
bass line so I was gonna say you know if
people are going to go into college and
get a degree I I think I would actually
push Computer Engineering over compsi or
even cyber security I'd agree with that
I don't disagree with that yeah
that's good
um okay
getting back over over to the list over
here
um so I guess let's go let's talk a
little bit about your combination of uh
writing and hacking right so I know we
talked a little bit about sort of
copywriting and like uh just this whole
concept of trying to develop yourself as
a writer
um and then you know you kind of wrote
all these Twitter threads that went Mega
viral a while back so any any tips or
tricks to share with the hacker
Community about the importance of
writing or how to write well as hacker
yeah I mean when I was writing those
Twitter threads I got so much Flack from
people about like oh you oversimplified
this or like did you really I got a lot
oh yeah there's lots of people that were
like making fun of me or
um honestly making fun of me just like
give me crap or just saying oh they're
like oh did the intern write this like
uh like people were very
um dang dude I don't know I guess being
uh what's I don't even know what the
word uh describe that is but that's
totally fine with me because like that's
not who I was writing for right so like
you have all these people who write like
these like Immaculate like technical
um writings as kind of just like a I
don't need to stroke my own ego and try
to sound as technical as possible
because like okay you write that you're
making your audience you're alienating
people who can understand that you're
alienating first off you're alienating a
huge audience and you're also only
writing for like
a really small number of people who
might be on the same level as you yeah
and like my whole purpose of writing
these Twitter threads were to
um I guess figure out how to explain
things clearly
and um yeah and simplify it to reach a
larger larger audience may get people
interested in bug bounties get them
interested in hacking yeah and like also
have them still be able to like
understand it and get like intrigued in
it and maybe want to try and learn some
of this right and
um yeah and I think you didn't simplify
it you know too much it's not like okay
I went to you know the internet and
found this directory you know it's like
no here's the you know here's the exact
like SubFinder command I used here's the
exact Dow command I used yeah I know
yeah and it's like and so I think it's a
really nice balance of like
um technical content in storytelling
which is it you know until you've tried
it you don't really know how difficult
it is because it's it's very challenging
yeah I spent a lot of time writing those
threads like I think the fastest one I
wrote was like 55 minutes
um which was like probably maybe like a
waste of time but no it was like really
good
to practice
um because it's such like technical
writing but still writing in a way
that's
intriguing and you know like yeah yeah I
think that's a great I think that's a
great skill I mean being able to
Captivate an audience is really powerful
and it's not something it's not a skill
that's that's very commonly you know
paired with a high level of technical
ability and so um I think that's you
know one of the uh one of the podcasts
that I listen to on a regular basis is
my first million and it was talking
about how yeah okay I love that pod and
um one of the things that they've talked
about just from a framework perspective
is like you don't have to be the best at
hacking or the best at blockchain or the
the best at any of these other things
you just have to take
you know a above average ability here
and combine it with an above average
ability over here and now you've got a
mixed skill set that's really unique and
marketable yeah and I think your ability
to do something like that
um with this writing is really I think
that's that's amazing
um so nice stuff there and and so I mean
do you really largely credit sampar's uh
copy this or whatever it is writing
course copy that or copy that yeah that
course is really good so yeah that's
that's
um a big reason why
um
yeah I took that course
and then I wanted to try applying it to
something pretty technical yeah and so
yeah I mean that was that was a pretty
yeah it's a great course I still go back
and go through it um or at least like
pieces of it to kind of just like refine
writing skills um I think everyone
should take a course on
copywriting just because it's like just
writing effectively I guess like you
don't need to be super long-winded
um
yeah I think it's I think it's a good a
good course
um yeah but at the same time
that's like this is a problem I have
with Twitter right now is that
everyone's becoming marketedy Mark
Market it Market Market marketing
marketery yes everything's like a
marketing thread now and it's like you
have to have this good combination of
like effective writing but I I like
actual substance genuinely yeah yeah
because like I've seen so many like oh
bar just killed gpt4 like oh my gosh
it's everyone here's 10 prompts you can
use this just like
all this noise of like you don't really
like
everything's supposed to be like when
everyone's doing the same thing it's
just I don't know it's just so it gets
to it gets to be just being yeah yeah
you can tell marketing material versus
like you know actual substance material
substance is still like
captivating I guess yeah lots of lots of
bloat out there I think and and so
taking this this ability to do
copywriting or uh you know effectually
tell a story and convey and Captivate an
audience and transporting this into
report writing so yeah you know I I'm
interesting to see how I'm interesting
to hear your opinion on how that's
affected the severity of your reports
and I will just before I let you answer
that I will say nogly is a big proponent
for this as well and you you just you
gotta I've collapsed with not only on a
couple of reports and I'll write some
stuff down and he's like no no no how do
you ever exactly no no no no how do you
ever how do you ever get critical
reports when you write like this and
nogly just kind of like rewrites it in
like very strongly States everything yes
and I think that's one Extreme as well
and it definitely works for him but
um what what are your thoughts on you
know the value of copywriting and and
storytelling in the context of a
technical report
yeah so like for me I don't really do
like it's not storytelling in my report
it's like very technical but
oh it's technical where it needs to be
right so like the summary might not be
as technical like okay I found this bug
well uh this is what it it does this is
I guess how it works and that's like
pretty technical but like summary and
then the impact are not maybe like
more like copywriting but it's just more
just very clear straightforward to the
point writing where it's like this is
the impact this is what you can do XYZ
where you're listening explicitly why
this is a critical and what your
specific views are on that because like
this is why I think um I talked to
someone about this or we had a whole
like talk at
um I think it was one of the hacker
Advisory board meetings yeah about the
impact section and the purpose of the
impact section people were like oh well
like it doesn't make sense to me because
like I just write my impact in the
summary and like well for me in my
impact section like all right either
like I'll just okay maybe I'll have if
I'm lazy I'll just write basically what
I had in the summary sure otherwise like
if it's like an actual a critical report
I will list out every single metric in
the CVS
um uh piece yeah yeah piece that I've
like selected I'll explain why I have it
set to that and why it should stay set
as that and then
if the program disagrees with me they'll
at least have an exact very clear
response back of why they disagree or
why that should be changed and that
leads that helps a lot with like
disagreements on severity
um big great tip there I mean I I rarely
go to that level of detail but in the
times that I have it's really made those
triage or misunderstandings that
sometimes get your report downgraded or
programmed misunderstandings that
sometimes get your report down in grade
data it's really minimized to those so
I'm actually going to write myself a
note right now to go in and do that for
the next live hacking event because
especially when you're at the live
hacking events and like reports are
flying all over the place
you know it gets really it gets really
tricky to have those you know complex
CVSs conversations and if you provide
justification for each metric that's the
word you're looking for metric yep
metrics thank you
um yeah and and if you provide
explanations for each one of those
metrics then I think it could really
provide a lot of clarity
yeah
yeah it forces the program to really to
really like dive deep and like actually
consider your report rather than like
okay yeah we have this bug
um
I don't know it like really forces them
to think through all the different
aspects that maybe they haven't thought
through before so yeah for sure
um solid uh let's talk a little bit
about more about your hacking
methodology and then I also want to talk
about some entrepreneurial pieces as
well because that's something you and I
have sort of bonded over yeah being
hackers and entrepreneurs at the same
time so
um that's something that that I'd like
to talk about as well
um so
I guess just talking a little bit more
about the Recon flow we touched on this
a little bit earlier but you know you're
going out there you're doing recon and
this is a quote that we quote almost
every episode I love this quote from Jay
haddocks the whole point of Recon is to
find my applications to hack right and
so when do you stop and actually
intentionally hack an application versus
continuing to Recon and um yeah we'll
break that question off there
yeah because that's a that's a really
hard I think that's
a hard skill to learn for beginners is
when to stop doing recon and when to
start hacking because it's really easy
to get into the like pattern of like
okay I'm just gonna run sub finder I'm
gonna write F off and everything totally
um and just like keep finding until like
maybe you like somehow find like a git
directory on some host or something
right right right right right
um so
I guess
it's pretty difficult
um to Define
like what exactly will make me stop but
a lot of times it's just like intuition
sure so you see like I'm doing like
directory brute forcing
um I've used like three word lists not
finding much
um
uh maybe I'll just like hop to the next
host
um oh I found interesting director on
this so like maybe it's like um
like a react app on this like
subdirectory and then you can go through
the JavaScript files and start actually
hacking and doing like normal
um actual like
hacking your hacking methodology or like
pen testing methodology I guess yeah um
yeah and then yeah it's just kind of
just this like intuition flow that I
have kind of nailed down
um sometimes I'm lazy it's like okay I
don't I'm just gonna run FF on a bunch
of different hosts and just do it that
way or I can just do in the background
while I'm looking at something else too
that was the follow-up question to this
was like okay so you know you found a
couple things and or you know you found
you know you're you're 40 or 50 hosts
you're going to assess and you you go to
each host and you
kind of do smart FF instead of like
normal FF where you you go to the hose
you know you're not just brute forcing
on slash uh you know always sometimes
you're going to the host and you're
saying okay well the index page
redirects to slash
you know dashboard but then it gives an
error or something like that so you
actually Brute Force dashboard
um yeah it's not like oh it's an images
directory I'm Gonna Keep right something
like you don't you don't want to waste
your your bandwidth doing that so but
like how many would you say like you
know you describe two extremes there you
say you described you know finding a
specific application and then just
really sort of going deep on that based
off of your intuition and you also
describe just sort of brute forcing
everything
um you know where do you think the
average sits like of like all right I'm
normally brute forcing like three to
four applications at a time or 10 or 20
or one at a time and really just reading
all the JavaScript files while it's
running
yeah I typically just do one at a time
really okay for the most that's cool
yeah so I I will I I think focus is also
really important yeah and that's
dangerous when you try to go after too
many things at too many times like
you're just gonna miss things so
um typically I can get a pretty good
feel for
you know like
what I want to hack on so it's like I'll
do my reconnaissance and it's kind of
just this process of like filtering all
this data down to like a single thing at
a time
um and so I will typically do Recon
until I find a host that's interesting
then I'll do Recon on that host and so
I'll do like directory Brute four scene
if there's like dashboard on it then
I'll start like reading through
JavaScript files and just start like
hacking it solid um then when I'm sick
of that single one I'll go hop to
something else that's that's cool to
hear because I I definitely didn't see
your methodology that way I figured
you'd be doing you know directory brute
forcing across multiple hosts you know
uh 10 20 hosts on a regular basis but
for you and I think this is something
really cool to highlight with Corbin's
methodology here is that he's a he's a
little bit of a Recon hacker but he also
is like sort of a deep Recon hacker
right because you're going you're going
to a host you're doing a lot of
directory brute forcing you're doing a
lot of you know enumeration but also
you're doing that in a smart way you
know you're reading the JavaScript
you're you're you know recursively brute
forcing on folders you found that sort
of thing and and keeping your attention
on one host which I think is really I
think that's key yeah or also like
adjacent hosts as well so like
Javascript file may reference some other
apis yeah like working on those too
because it's all a part of this like one
um that's great Tech application so so
you're you're you're taking you know
you're breaking apart the JS file you're
saying okay these are the Json hosts to
this the hosts that work on the specific
or that power this specific website and
you're using you know text from the
other page using references from that JS
file to enable itself on the apis as
well yeah exactly yeah so that's that's
pretty huge too because there will be so
many like API endpoints you'll never be
able to guess yeah almost out you know
all this other like contextual all these
all these other contextual pieces so man
I got I gotta find this uh this tweet
from from you I I was just reading
through
um some of your tweets that you that you
put out uh previously and and it was
like oh here it is right here I'll link
it to you hold on uh I'm gonna send it
to you in Discord
uh scroll down and we'll put this tweet
in the description as well this is
Corbin's um Corbin's tweet on hacking
the military
um but scroll down to like scroll down
to like the fourth or no it's a third
tweet and it says yeah after reading the
JS files in directory before saying I
came across this endpoint scorm 2004
upload course.aspx and I'm like what do
you what do you want is that was that if
you're brute forcing like no how did you
so but you got that aspx file from
reading the the JS file and then I guess
maybe you found the full path by like
brute forcing some directories and such
yeah and so like I
one thing that I do that I don't know if
anyone else does is
um I'll find a like a directory called
like JavaScript and I'll just I'll Brute
Force for JavaScript files oh that's big
so
um I've done that and also I've tried to
find CSS files because sometimes I'll do
like import like image from like this
it'll be like some like super long
directory that like you might not be
able to find but yeah I think I was I I
was brute forcing through four
JavaScript files and I
I had
like come across a new directory with
like JavaScript files and I brute force
them in there
um then that's when I came across that
um aspx okay so you you actually brute
force or the JS files which led you to
this more complex aspx endpoint yep yep
so it's like going through JavaScript
files to find some endpoints and then
brute forcing those and then in one of
those there's like a reference to that
nice that's a great takeaway I like that
um
nice man
um well that's so we're we're at about
an hour now um I did have one other
sort of status of yours that are um uh
post of yours that I wanted to look at
um
you know what but I think we're gonna
save this one for for a different time
because I did want to follow up on some
entrepreneurial stuff as well so
currently so okay a couple a couple
months back you announced breachless AI
and I kind of want to I kind of want to
hear about some lessons learned from
that because it seems like you pivoted
over to boring mattress code now which I
also I love and I'll hold up my my phone
for the YouTube video I've got wearing
mattress pill on the back of my phone
and I've actually had a couple people
ask me about it already so you're
getting free marketing off of this yes
thank you
but uh you know what happened to
breachless.ai and what what kind of
lessons did you learn from that
yeah so I'll first introduce it too
because people may not know yeah yeah so
breachless the idea behind that was that
I was going to use
um
artificial artificial intelligence
artificial intelligence artificial
intelligence to um basically the idea
was to do analysis of incoming emails
um and adding
um
well let's take a step behind the
currency was like it was to help prevent
social engineering attacks right and so
like you have companies like no before
um like all these different companies
that are doing these uh what are they
called so uh security awareness
trainings yeah yeah um and so it's like
you force uh employees to go through
really boring outdated videos that are
like 20 years old or they're just like
really like
irrelevant to like the average person
like a hacker who might think oh wow
these are like really funny these are
really cool and you have Your Average
Joe's like this is the stupidest thing
I've ever had to watch what I have to
watch this
um then the problem too is like okay
yeah you watched a video
four times a year and you never remember
it in the moment and so my idea was to
add
um context to uh actual emails in like
the form of a banner to help people
identify social engineering
um attacks or potential social
engineering attacks
um just like write in each email
um and so that was the idea there
um it didn't go very far I had actually
had a pretty sizable wait list I think I
had
like
200 to 300 nice dude companies on that
way oh that's a lot actually yeah yeah
it was it was actually it was actually
pretty decent there's some pretty like
decent sized companies on that
um but what made me move away from it
was I wanted to bootstrap the company I
didn't want to raise
um Venture Capital yeah and
um
it was also a pretty crowded space just
fishing anti-fishing stuff
yeah just like email security stuff I
don't think that necessarily should have
like maybe
turn me away so much but I think the
biggest issue was
um the requirements for a lot of
companies have for like stock two audits
so what is that
it's like basically companies
um when they want
to use uh let's see like I don't want to
mess it up sure while you're looking at
it's like it's a compliance it's like a
compliance standard
um which is like how organizations
manage like data yeah and so like you
have to go through this like compliance
process
um
and be able to like provide this to each
customer that like asks for it
um gotcha and so that costs at least
like 150 000 and I didn't really want to
pay that out of pocket with and
um you know without VC uh develop an MVP
and then have you know have to pay 150
000 out of pocket just just for that
like that's a pretty big expense out of
pocket especially without
um raising money and that's a huge
barrier to enter yeah geez yeah it's a
very yeah it's it's big and
um there are people I think that I think
you can find an auditor like you could
probably give like Equity to and pay
them a lot less but
um yeah with that it was just kind of
like a turn off and
he was talking about getting back into
the mattress in the mattress space um
yeah and so
um I jumped over to that and I was also
very intrigued by you know like consumer
goods so I thought that would be cool
sleep is such a cool thing to go after
too like I feel like that is is such an
amazing industry yeah yeah yeah so
hopped over to that I still think the
breeches product the idea there is
pretty cool
um if someone can like I can see the the
gears turning in your head still like as
you're talking about I know I still love
it yeah I still love the idea and I
don't think it's a bad idea it's just
like
you know maybe someday yeah would you
would you consider selling or handing
off that that email list of or wait list
of of companies uh to somebody who
wanted to take a stab at breach list
yeah I mean I'd still be interested in
like being involved with it someone it's
just uh like do you want to raise like
Venture Capital it's just like a whole
nother completely different than you
know dude yeah well there you go if any
of you other hackers out there are
interested in an entrepreneurial
opportunity I I love the product I think
it would be really I think it's a really
good fit you know having a an email
Banner having some sort of add-on for G
Suite or from for Outlook and and you
know who knows Microsoft might just have
this in there now with gpt4 they'll be
able to do that too yeah well that's the
other thing is I I feel like maybe my
timelines are a little off but did you
launch this before Chad gbt blew up
I think it was I think it was about
about I think it was about yeah at least
it was very early yeah it was really
early I don't I it was before chat gbt
was released yeah and so that that's man
that had GPT three yeah on the API for
that and that was it that was a great
timing of the market I think you know
like it it you know that before that
whole thing blew up you know you had
already launched this and and so yeah
yeah man I I'm I've still got I've still
got high hopes for it I would love to
see it at some point
um pop up so definitely let me know if
you're if you're getting back into it
again because I think that'd be really I
think that'd be a really cool
um thing to be involved with and also
you know I hope you find someone in the
industry who's got the bandwidth to take
it on uh because I would love to use it
in an organization
yeah
um all right I guess the the other
question that I have is like what what
um
what sort of hacker entrepreneurial
takeaways did you did you have from that
experience of pivoting like did you was
that a hard move for you to Pivot away
from it I I could see a little bit of uh
uh cognitive dissonance I think in in
your eyes
yeah I mean um
it wasn't
it's different because like it's still I
still like the idea but I'm also
like
I don't know where it
I said like I'm so optimistic but I'm
like pessimistic in other ways because
like yeah the cyber security field is
like extremely saturated from where it
used to be uh but at the same time I
like the idea a lot and I think
it could be very helpful but then I'm
also like pessimistic about like okay
why can't Microsoft just add that yeah
which I think they very well could now
now I think they probably Liberation I
think with all their Integrations is
okay it's probably a good thing I did
step away from it but you know
um there's definitely Market risk there
I I think you know oh yeah you could
easily get replaced by a big player um
or yeah exactly you could get acquired
by a big player you know that's the
other thing and yeah for someone who
wants like a quick quick integration
yeah
um so I mean I
I'm not like
I guess worried about it it didn't it
was actually relatively easy for me to
to Pivot jump away it was
um
first is like it's a little
a little sad because I like the idea
yeah at the same time I was like I had
all these other kind of like had some
doubts
um but yeah yeah I knew it's where I
needed to go next and I guess how to
just trust my gut on that yeah for sure
man well I I'm glad to see that you you
know were able to successfully assess
the the difficulties of that specific
challenge in pivot and I'm excited to
see where Boring Mattress Co is headed
do you have any any update on that last
I heard you you got your prototype out
to the house
yes it's super comfy I've been sleeping
on it for
a while now yeah I love it it's super
super so I mean are you gonna make a lot
more are you gonna make much
modification to that mattress or are you
guys going to just move forward with it
um not to the mattress itself I think
we're still
um iterating on the cover so that's like
the outside of it that's like
um you have like on your phone there's
like firestock on it
um and then the cover is like the the
outside like the aesthetic we're still
figuring out that
um that piece of it yeah we're not gonna
take any yeah I I think um Let me let me
just let me just go ahead and add my my
two cents to the mattress uh industry
here I I got these bed sheets and and
this is bed sheets so it's a different
different Arena but who knows maybe you
could do a package deal or something no
we we will probably get some point and
so I've got these bed sheets and for one
there's like this these bamboo bed
sheets that are just super like
cool and a cool meaning like you know
not like the opposite of hot not like
cool as in yeah amazing not like yeah
they're very cool you know like and
they're awesome and I love them and it
really helps me sleep better but also
they have this little pocket on the side
of the bed it's built into you know the
side of the mattress the fitted sheet or
um the fitted sheet for them that goes
on the mattress and it's perfect size to
like put your phone in and it's just
like such a nice little thing you know
you're in bed you got your phone and you
just slide it right into this pocket
next huh so anyway there's your little
tidbit you know cut me in whenever you
make millions off of that
um and uh yeah we'll be good
um cool well dude thanks for coming on
to the pot I I tried to you know uh
dedicate this last section to the boring
mattress company uh but um you got any
other shout outs you wanna you wanna
make
not really solid shout out to everyone
hacking out there yeah well you can find
Corbin at uh you know twitter.com hacker
underscore and then uh boring mattress
company is twitter.com boringmattress
which somehow you got that's awesome uh
that's because no one in that industry
is going to admit that mattresses are
boring yeah that's true they they've got
that's yeah also I like their brand
that's a great Mark yeah and I love the
copy as well on the on the description
for the for your Twitter page so I'll
I'll let uh I won't even read it out
loud I'll just say for those listening
yeah go go to the page follow the
account and read the the description
because it's I think it's a great
example of of engaging copy so
all right man well thanks for coming on
appreciate it
yeah thanks for having me that's the pod
[Music]
that was a great episode with Corbin uh
always love having him on the Pod if you
enjoyed this content please head over to
youtube.com critical thinking podcast
drop a like And subscribe and also don't
forget to stay engaged on your podcast
app of choice via subscribing or
following or whatever it is you do the
podcast realm is a little weird so just
I'm sure you'll figure it out thanks see
y'all next week
[Music]